## **Huynh Minh Tam**

Software Engineer

A passionate software engineer with more than half year of hands-on experience as a FRONT-END developer. My expertise spans Javascript /TypeScript programming languages and extends to another programming languages . Always excited to tackle new challenges in the ever-evolving world of tech.

### **Work Experience**

Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam 0823532831 hunhminhtam@gmail.com

Sep 2023 - Dec 2023 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

#### Intern Frontend Developer

**FPT** software

• At FPT Software, I'm learning to design effective UX/UI, implementing interfaces from Figma, and developing modules like CRUD.

Mar 2024 - Jun 2024 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

#### Frontend Developer

Cydeva technology

 At Cydeva technology. Skilled in developing and maintaining projects. Proficient in both front-end and back-end technologies, with expertise in Typescript/Javascipt programming languages and a bit mobile development.

#### Education

Dec 2020 - Dec 2024

FPT University
Software Engineering

GPA:8.2/10

#### Skills

Backend	Frontend	Other
<ul> <li>JavaScipt /TypeScipt</li> </ul>	HTML/CSS	MySQL ,Mongo DB
<ul><li>Java</li></ul>	<ul><li>NextJS / ReactJS</li></ul>	<ul> <li>RabbitMQ</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Node js express</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Redux toolkit / Zustand</li> </ul>	Socket IO
	<ul> <li>React Query /SWR</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Github CI/CD</li> </ul>
	<ul> <li>Tailwind CSS / Mui / Ant design</li> </ul>	<ul><li>Cloudinary</li></ul>
		<ul> <li>Github/Gitlab</li> </ul>

# Projects

Apr 2024 - Present thehostie.com Hostie Fullstack developer	Hostie is my entrepreneurial project aimed at connecting brokers and property owners in the short-term accommodation sector. Utilizing technologies like Golang and Java, Hostie enhances communication and operational efficiency, demonstrating my capability to innovate and integrate advanced solutions in hospitality management
Jan 2023 – March 2023 Hella Booking Backend Developer	School project .Experienced in Hella backend development, Hella external api development.
Aug 2024 - Oct 2024 Pc store Fullstack developer CERTIFICATIONS	My pet project based on <a href="https://tinhocngoisao.com/">https://tinhocngoisao.com/</a> . Webapp is a small ecommerce platforms.

Apr 2023	CertNexus Certified Ethical Emerging Technologies
Jan 2023	Software Development Lifecycle
Oct 2022	Web Design for Everybody
Jun 2022	Computer Communications
DEC 2021	Toeic 610

## **SOCIAL NETWORK**

Gitub: https://github.com/TamHM1410

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/toilatam1410/